I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
"Condor Ramen"
Here you go!
Thanks!
Pops...I'm so grateful. Thank you!
Don't mention it.
You work really hard for me.
Being in a band costs so much?
Yeah...Until your band starts selling,
it's really hard.
The other night, there were more people
in the band than there were customers.
Are you...in your right mind?
So this is the girl? Girls are scary...
Oh! W-what's this?!
Taira-kun! Taira-kun!
-What was that?
-So scary...
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
Taira-kun...
Dying Breed's...coming to Japan...
-Taira-kun!
-Huh? What's with him?
Taira-kun...
-Oh...sorry. It's a friend.
-Taira-kun!
Hey, Chiba, what's the matter?
Wow! Dying Breed's finally
performing in Japan?
Isn't it great?
"Dying Breed:
Japan Concert Schedule Announced"
"Popular American Rock Group"
Isn't it great?
"Dying Breed:
Japan Concert Schedule Announced"
"Popular American Rock Group"
Yeah. It's great.
"Dying Breed:
Japan Concert Schedule Announced"
"Popular American Rock Group"
Yeah...
We'd better be sure to go see them.
Yeah!
I wonder if that Ryusuke
will introduce us to Eddy.
Well, I doubt it.
After all, Dying Breed is the greatest band
in the U.S. With sales of 8 million copies.
But...He's a friend of Eddy's, right?
-But to think that Dying Breed
is coming to Japan...
-Yeah...
-Tachi High and Toyonaga West High?
-Yes.
-I'd like to try for one of them.
-Dangerous!
The way your grades stand,
you're hanging on to the borderline
by the skin of your teeth.
Skin of my teeth?
It'll all depend on how hard
you work this summer.
Oh...
Thank you.
Hey! I'm not through with you!!
I hear you're in a band.
Are you aiming to become a pro?
Well...
Ridiculous! There's no way you can make it.
I've been teaching for 20 years.
I don't know of a single one
of my students who has become a singer.
That's the reality...Tanaka.
"Music Room"
"Light Music Club Room"
Hyodo-kun...He's gotten even better.
Saku...
Baumkuchen...
You talking about the cake?
No. It was a band that was popular
when we were around three or four.
Hmm...Maybe I've heard of them,
but maybe not.
The guitarist in that band was
Masato Kohinata...Hyodo's dad.
But their last names are different.
Yeah. Seems Hyodo is
his mother's last name.
Why?
His mother's been divorced twice.
That's why...
Boy, you sure know a lot.
Oh, Tanaka-kun! Sakurai-kun!
What's wrong?
Won't you perform at our
Cultural Festival in the fall?
What?
I'm on the executive committee this year.
We're going to turn the
talent show into a contest,
and we'll choose the top guitarist,
vocalist, and even the top band. And so...
...please be sure to participate!
-Uh...
-Yes!!
Huh?!
Top guitarist?
All we need is...get into the night
People need it...get into the night
-Hey, you free tomorrow?
-People need it...get into the night
-Huh? Sorry! I have
something important to do.
-People need it...get into the night
-What's so important?
-All we need is...get into the night
-Can't tell you!
-Hey! This is important too.
-All we need is...get into the night
-It's really important!
-People need it...get into the night
-This is really, really important!
-It's super, ultra, heavyweight important!
-People need it...get into the night
We got to move in a...
Koyuki, are you all right?
Mm...
You look pale.
To tell you the truth, I have
trouble with all these rides.
Then what's the fun
in coming to an amusement park?
Well...
I want to ride that thing!
Huh? Another ride?
I can handle this.
But...my legs are getting tired.
Maho, are you sure you're pedaling?
Maho...chan...Are you all right?
Mm...I'm fine...
You do have a fever.
It's only a slight fever.
I'm sorry to worry you.
Silly.
Why'd you come here
knowing you had a fever?
Well...
Are you sure you can make it home alone?
Yeah. My dad says he'll
pick me up at the station.
I see. Then I don't have to worry.
Koyuki...Do you remember
that swim meet?
I remember, but...I think
I owe my win that day to you.
Mm...Not about that...about our wager.
Huh?
I told you, didn't I? If you won,
I'd do anything you wanted me to.
I want you to work toward
becoming a pro, along with me.
I can't do that.
Why not? You sing well, and your English
is good...and you're cute.
I'm sure you could become a pro.
I...I'm different from you.
Just look at you...You're terrific.
Are you all right?
Mm...
-Please don't stop
in the middle of the 50-meter pool.
-Saito-san, what was your first kiss like?
Just thinking about it gets me so mad!
She was a woman, easily over 40,
from Yoshiwara.
Damn you! Give me back my youth!
Saito-san...
...corner where stars fall
I sing again today
A melody drawn on the street
Rise up to the sky
A love song you can hear in the wind
-Eiji!
-Eiji-kun!
-A love song you can hear in the wind
A stage on clouds, a neon dance
-Manabu!
-With all my prayers for you
I continue to sing
If you cannot sing from the heart
Why sing at all?
I can still feel you
-Boy, there sure are a lotta girls!
-I can still feel you
-Still so strong
-Nothing like the number
Beck can draw in.
-Still so strong
-Manabu!
-Days of endless memories
-Belle Ame? This...
-You must have become a star
-This isn't rock.
-These words, these painful memories
-But they're set to make a major debut.
-Let it reach you
-Ryusuke...Take a look.
That's Ran, formerly of Noir.
Noir's CD sales have been monumental
in the music industry.
Wow! They have the backing of the
leading figure in the world of visual rock?
On the street corner where stars fall
-I have to get to work, so I'm leaving.
-On the street corner where stars fall
-I sing again today
-I have work too.
A melody drawn on the street
Rise up to the sky
-Eiji...Is this the "ultimate band"
you were talking about?
-Rise up to the sky
-Eiji...Is this the "ultimate band"
you were talking about?
-A love song you can hear in the wind
A stage on clouds, a neon dance
With all my prayers for you
I continue to sing
If you cannot sing...
Yukio! You have a call from Minami-san.
Okay!
Hey!
Sorry I'm late.
Shall we go?
Hello? Yeah. Oh, for real?
That's great, but...You know the place?
Uh-huh...Okay. Then I'll see you around.
Maho?
Huh? No. A friend.
Hm...
-Isn't it exciting?
-But, you think they'll really come?
-Ah...I can't wait!
-Yeah.
There are so many people today.
I took a peek out there,
and the crowd is amazing.
Is there going to be such
an exciting band playing tonight?
We're not that popular, right?
Eddy's coming.
-What?
-Huh?
Uh...It's true Dying Breed
is here in Japan, but...
Hmm...
Word probably got out.
Those customers are here to see Eddy.
Are you joking?
Is that...for real?
That's great!
Hey! You'd better not be pulling our leg!
I thought the pressure'd
be too much for you.
Pressure? You idiot!
If Eddy Lee of Dying Breed is here,
this is a terrific chance
for us to get ourselves known!
Chiba-kun...
We'll just have to go for it.
That's right.
One, two...
Uh! Typhoon...Typhoon 24...
24-7, non-stop!
We're gonna rush at you!
Gonna send you flyin'!
Lift up your heavy ass, now
If you take off that stiff head
You'll feel totally loose
This crazy, crazy world
You just have to Stage Dive or Die
Mind blower, a shower of sweat
Run towards a new world, my life
Those who seek it will be rewarded
Pass the hot shot
Keep on coming, come on!
Blow your mind
Squeeze your sweat yeah
-Koyuki!
-Blow your mind
Squeeze your sweat
Find the way you are,
spice of your life
Heavy beat, hey come on people
Find the way you are,
spice of your life
Heavy beat, hey come on people
Yeah take your spice
Hm...Oh!
Hey, Maho...It's been a long time.
-Hey!
-How've you been?
Idiot!
-It's Eddy Lee!
-I knew it!
-I can't believe it!
-Wow!
-Can I have your autograph?
-Hi!
Ray!
Oh shit! Maho...Tell them
to shut up. I'll sign it later.
Okay.
Will you all pipe down?
Eddy's here to hear the performance.
Poor band.
Should I splash it to them?
Aww, dude. Don't make any more trouble
or else the tour's gonna be suspended, yo.
Did you know, Koyuki?
They say Matt didn't like the PA
in a Swedish live house, so he just left.
After one number, he said,
"See you tomorrow,"and left.
It's doesn't look like we can
go on with our performance.
You're right...Shall we call them up?
Uh-huh...
No. This is our stage.
-Koyuki!
-Huh?
We'll skip a number and go to "Face."
Okay!
Maho...
Running over, sometimes
Feels like you leave me behind
Now you don't have to mind it
Find you shining, everyday by day
Sing it up, my sister
In this world which everyone is lonely
Everything will be fine someday
Remember playing...
Your song was good,
but your guitar was the pits.
-I hear it's good.
-You serious?
Why do you know everything? Aw, shut up!
I like your voice.
You could be a good singer...
if you get some more practice.
Thank you...so much.
Well, see ya.
Maho...Translate that, will you?
Your guitar needs work.
But your singing's not bad.
Huh? Really? Eddy said that?!
Are you all right?
Ray, that was...
Is Matt all right?
It's like...a dream...
To think that Eddy and Matt of
Dying Breed were here in my place...
Eddy's autograph...Don't you dare erase it!
Of course I won't! It's my treasure!
But I want to clean up
Matt's mess as soon as I can.
Hey, Ray...Could I borrow Lucille?
What...are you serious?
Dude, the show today
totally made me wanna play.
But if they found that out,
they'd come and kill you.
Yeah, you're right...
Yeah. It might be crazy.
Yeah...
Man, I don't know what's
so great about those clothes.
Well that one looks gorgeous to me.
Oh, yeah...Those are okay.
Huh?!
Oh!
Hmph! Bassist...
Matt looks really drunk.
I wonder if he doesn't like me.
Mm...He probably won't remember.
Dude, day after tomorrow,
there's gonna be a secret show.
You and your buddies should come by.
Oh, can we?
Yeah, totally Ray.
Today was so much fun.
Okay, I'll see you at the live show.
Man, we should really
get back to the hotel.
Bye, everybody!
There, right before my eyes,
are Eddy and Matt!
This is reality! It's not a dream!
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Hey, everybody!
What karaoke songs do you sing?
"Live 12 'Secret Live"'
Hey, everybody!
What karaoke songs do you sing?
"Live 12 'Secret Live"'
I...Heh-heh-heh...Well, I...